A Guide to the Louise Wright Bailey Genealogical Collection
Roanoke Public Libraries
Roanoke Public Libraries
Louise Bailey Genealogical Collection
Roanoke Public Libraries
2014.1.6.2
12 record storage boxes
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Louise Wright Bailey.
Biographical Note
Louise Wright Bailey was born on 13 August 1928 in Roanoke, Virginia. She was a graduate of Jefferson High School, Roanoke College and the University of North Carolina at Greensboro (then the Women’s College of the University of North Carolina), from which she graduated with a Bachelor’s degree in Economics. As the wife of Harry Bailey for almost 60 years, Louise lived in various states across the country and traveled extensively as a result of Harry’s army career. Louise was an avid genealogist who began her research in the early 1970s. Due to living in many locations, she was able to visit institutions housing collections relevant to her research. She, along with her brother, Fred Boyer Wright, Sr. and sister Julia Wright Wells, published a history of the Straley-Wright Families. She continued collecting genealogical information until the early 2000s. Louise Wright Bailey passed away on 30 January 2012 in McLean, Virginia.
Scope and Content
The Louise Bailey Collection consists of 12 record storage boxes which include family group sheets, records, correspondence, news clippings, photographs, handwritten research notes, birth, marriage and death announcements and photocopies of publications related to Mrs. Bailey’s research. Some of the primary surnames included in the research are: Bailey, Boyer, Cook, Cornett, Farley, French, Romine, Straley, Thompson, Vaught and Wright, as well as many other connected surnames from the 1600s to the early 1900s. The majority of the collection focuses on Southwest Virginia, though other parts of Virginia, other states and some European connections are represented. Mrs. Bailey maintained excellent organization of her genealogical research materials, which was further maintained in the processing of this collection. It is also important to note that in many cases, source information was provided for this thorough genealogical collection. It should also be mentioned that much of the correspondence included in the collection contains genealogical information, as Mrs. Bailey received research requests from individuals all over the country. Records included in the collection are often handwritten transcriptions for official records, but in some cases may include photocopies of the records.
Please note that records from Virginia counties that became part of West Virginia in 1861 are filed with West Virginia records.
Arrangement
Documents are arranged by alphabetically by document type and in most cases by geographical location thereafter.
Please note that records from Virginia counties that became part of West Virginia in 1861 are filed with West Virginia records.
Index Terms
Container List
- (Box 1)
  - (Box 1 of 12)
    - Bible Records - Boyer Family (Folder 1)
    - Bible Records – McCraw, William C. and Emily D. (Folder 2)
    - Bibliography of published items donated with collection (Folder 3)
    - Birth Announcements (Folder 4)
    - Charts – Governor’s and Federal Officers, Congress and Academic Kinsmen (Folder 5)
    - Correspondence to Julia Wells from various authors (Folder 6)
  - Folders 7-53 contain correspondence to Louise Bailey arranged alphabetically by author’s last name. Where possible, topics and dates are given. (Box 1 of 12)
    - Anderson, Terry: Anderson Family, 1985 (Folder 7)
    - Bailey, Jennifer: Personal (Folder 8)
    - Bailey, Judith: Personal (Folder 9)
    - Blankenship, Althea: Wright Family (Folder 10)
    - Brammer, Mary: Bryan Family, 1979 (Folder 11)
    - Carter, Gladys: Vaught Family, 1981-1985 (Folder 12)
    - Cole, Dorothy: Meese and Vaught Families, 1976-1999 (Folder 13)
    - Cornett, Pam: Cornett Family, 1980 (Folder 14)
    - Custer, Mrs. John C.: Personal (Folder 15)
    - Dickinson, Jack: Vaught Family, 1981-1982 (Folder 16)
    - Dunaway, Jessie: Long and Vaught Families, 1981 (Folder 17)
    - Ferrell, Mary: Farley Family, 1987-1989 (Folder 18)
    - French, David: Vogt, Clemons and Trout Families (Folder 19)
    - Galloway, Peggy: Remine Family, 1982-1983 (Folder 20)
    - Gibson, Randy: Roman Family, 1984 (Folder 21)
    - Hale, Kerry: Anderson Family, 1979-1984 (Folder 22)
    - Harland, Mary M.: McCraw Family, 1983-1984 (Folder 23)
    - Howell, Louise: Romine Family, 1979 (Folder 24)
    - Jones, James: Bryan Family, 1979-1980 (Folder 25)
    - Knutsen, Elna: Personal (Folder 26)
    - Knutsen, Torbjorn: Personal (Folder 27)
    - Lamb, Mary: Vaught Family, 1985 (Folder 28)
    - McConnell, Iris: Vaught Family (Folder 29)
    - McDaniel, Lois: Horsley Family, 1986 (Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1991 (Folder 31)
    - Myers, Lola: Long Family, 1985 (Folder 32)
    - O’Brien, Erma: Personal (Folder 33)
    - O’Connell, Phyliss: Sutherland Family (Folder 34)
    - Patterson, Mildred: Boyer and Wright Families, 1979 (Folder 35)
    - Payne, James: Payne Family, 1978 (Folder 36)
    - Pinion, Rose: Thompson and Straley Families, 2002-2003 (Folder 37)
    - Pope, Helen: Vaught Family (Folder 38)
    - Ramsey, Katherin: Bays Family, 1978 (Folder 39)
    - Remine, William: Remine Family, 1980 (Folder 40)
    - Skeens, Gloria B.: Senter Family (Folder 41)
    - Straley, C.: Straley Family, 1987 (Folder 42)
    - Sturgill, Lorene: Long and Boyer Families, 1981-1982 (Folder 43)
    - Stutsman, John: Anderson Family, 1989-1990 (Folder 44)
    - Surface, Pat: Rhudy, Rhodes and Wright Families (Folder 45)
    - Tuttle, Mary: Remine Family, 1982-1983 (Folder 46)
    - Unknown authors (Folder 47)
    - Wagner, Ellen: Straley and Madison Families, 1978-1997 (Folder 48)
    - Wells, Julia: Various families (Folder 49)
    - Wright, Fred: Various families (Folder 50)
    - Wright, Mrs. Lawrence Fielder: Wright Family, 1983-1988 (Folder 51)
    - Wright, Norene: Wright Family, 1981-1985 (Folder 52)
    - Wright, Sallie: Personal (Folder 53)
  - Folders 54-111 contain Family Group Sheets arranged alphabetically by surname.
    - Abbott (Folder 54)
    - Acord (Folder 55)
    - Adair (Folder 56)
    - Adams (Folder 57)
    - Adkins (Folder 58)
    - Akers (Folder 59)
    - Alba (Folder 60)
    - Albert (Folder 61)
    - Alderson (Folder 62)
    - Alexander (Folder 63)
    - Allen (Folder 64)
    - Allison (Folder 65)
    - Alvis (Folder 66)
    - Amick (Folder 67)
    - Anderson (Folder 68)
    - Andrews (Folder 69)
    - Applegate (Folder 70)
    - Archer (Folder 71)
    - Armentrout (Folder 72)
    - Arnold (Folder 73)
    - Arnoult (Folder 74)
    - Arrington (Folder 75)
    - Ashe (Folder 76)
    - Atha (Folder 77)
    - Atkins (Adkins) (Folder 78)
    - Atwell, Atwood, Auer, Austin, Avens, Avis, Ayers (Folder 79)
    - Baber, Baggerly, Bail (Folder 80)
    - Bailey – Given names ‘A’ to ‘G’ (Folder 81)
    - Bailey – Given names ‘H’ to ‘K’ (Folder 82)
    - Bailey – Given names ‘L’ to ‘Z’ (Folder 83)
    - Baker (Folder 84)
    - Ball, Ballard, Bane, Banks, Barber, Barger (Folder 85)
    - Barker (Folder 86)
    - Barley, Barlow, Barnes, Barnett, Barr, Barrett, Barton, Baskerville (Folder 87)
    - Baskett (Folder 88)
    - Bassham (Basham) (Folder 89)
    - Bateman, Baxter, Baylor, Bays, Beach (Folder 90)
    - Beasley (Folder 91)
    - Beatty (Folder 92)
    - Beavers, Bechett, Beckner (Folder 93)
    - Beggs, Behan, Belcher, Bell (Folder 94)
    - Bellany (Folder 95)
    - Bennett, Berry, Bettis (Folder 96)
    - Bevan (Folder 97)
    - Bibb, Bice (Folder 98)
    - Bigg(s) (Folder 99)
    - Billups, Birchfield, Bird, Black, Blackburn (Folder 100)
    - Blackmore (Blakemore) (Folder 101)
    - Blankenship (Folder 102)
    - Bloss, Bodenlamer, Body, Boggess, Bogle, Bolton, Book, Boon, Booth, Borders (Folder 103)
    - Bossert (Folder 104)
    - Boster, Botner, Bourne, Bowen, Bower, Bowling, Bowman, Boyd (Folder 105)
    - Boyer (Folder 106)
    - Boyer – Given names ‘A’ to ‘W’ (Folder 107)
    - Boyer – Unknown connections (Folder 108)
    - Braaten, Bradberry, Bradley, Bragg, Brammer, Branham, Bransford, Bratten, Brenamen, Bridges, Brinks (Folder 109)
    - Bromfield, Bromley, Brookman, Brooks, Brotherton (Folder 110)
    - Brown (Folder 111)
  - Family Group Sheets (Box 2 of 12)
    - Browning, Broyles (Folder 1)
    - Bruce, Brugh, Brunk (Folder 2)
    - Bryan (Brian, Bryant(s)) (Folder 3)
    - Bryson (Folder 4)
    - Bujicklian (Folder 5)
    - Cadle (Caddall), Cain (Folder 6)
    - Caldwell (Folder 7)
    - Buchanan, Buckland, Bulman, Buntner, Burchett, Burdett (Burditt), Burgess, Burks (Folder 8)
    - Burnett, Burns, Burnside, Burris, Burton, Burwell, Butler, Butt(s), Byrne, Byrneside (Folder 9)
    - Calfee, Call, Callicort, Calloway (Folder 10)
    - Campbell (Folder 11)
    - Canterbury (Folder 12)
    - Cantley (Folder 13)
    - Caperton (Folder 14)
    - Carbaugh (Folder 15)
    - Carden (Cardin) (Folder 16)
    - Carpenter (Folder 17)
    - Carper (Folder 18)
    - Carr (Folder 19)
    - Carrier (Folder 20)
    - Carson (Folder 21)
    - Carter (Folder 22)
    - Cartright (Folder 23)
    - Caruso (Folder 24)
    - Casey (Folder 25)
    - Cassaday (Folder 26)
    - Caudill (Cordell) (Folder 27)
    - Cawley (Cauley) (Folder 28)
    - Cave (Folder 29)
    - Cecil (Folder 30)
    - Chambers (Folder 31)
    - Chamblin (Folder 32)
    - Chanceaurline (Chanceleum) (Folder 33)
    - Chapel (Folder 34)
    - Chapman (Folder 35)
    - Chappin (Folder 36)
    - Charlton (Folder 37)
    - Chavey (Folder 38)
    - Cheatwood (Chitwood) (Folder 39)
    - Cheney (Folder 40)
    - Chewning (Folder 41)
    - Childers (Folder 42)
    - Chiles (Folder 43)
    - Christian (Folder 44)
    - Christie (Folder 45)
    - Cimo (Folder 46)
    - Clark (Folder 47)
    - Clay – Given names ‘A’ to ‘L’ (Folder 48)
    - Clay – Given names ‘M’ to ‘Z’ (Folder 49)
    - Claypool (Folder 50)
    - Clements (Folder 51)
    - Clifton (Folder 52)
    - Cline (Kline) (Folder 53)
    - Clyburn (Clibourne, Clybourn) (Folder 54)
    - Coburn (Folder 55)
    - Coffey (Folder 56)
    - Coffman (Folder 57)
    - Cogdill (Folder 58)
    - Colanero (Folder 59)
    - Cole (Folder 60)
    - Coleman (Folder 61)
    - Colley (Folder 62)
    - Collins (Folder 63)
    - Combs (Folder 64)
    - Comer (Folder 65)
    - Compton (Folder 66)
    - Conley (Folder 67)
    - Conner (Folder 68)
    - Conrad (Folder 69)
    - Cook(e) – Given names ‘A’ to ‘I’ (Folder 70)
    - Cook(e) – Given names ‘J’ to ‘W’ (Folder 71)
    - Cook(e) – Miscellaneous (Folder 72)
    - Cooley (Folder 73)
    - Cooper (Folder 74)
    - Coolston, Coontz (Folder 75)
    - Copely (Folder 76)
    - Copin, Corder, Cormer (Corner), Cornell (Folder 77)
    - Cornett(e) (Cornutt(e), Cornut, Carnet(t)(e), Kurnett, Karnett) – Given names ‘A’ to ‘E’ (Folder 78)
    - Cornett(e) (Cornutt(e), Cornut, Carnet(t)(e), Kurnett, Karnett) – Given names ‘F’ to ‘I’ (Folder 79)
    - Cornett(e) (Cornutt(e), Cornut, Carnet(t)(e), Kurnett, Karnett) – Given names ‘J’ to ‘K’ (Folder 80)
    - Cornett(e) (Cornutt(e), Cornut, Carnet(t)(e), Kurnett, Karnett) – Given names ‘L’ to ‘N’ (Folder 81)
    - Cornett(e) (Cornutt(e), Cornut, Carnet(t)(e), Kurnett, Karnett) – Given names ‘O’ to ‘T’ (Folder 82)
    - Cornett(e) (Cornutt(e), Cornut, Carnet(t)(e), Kurnett, Karnett) – Given names ‘V’ to ‘Z’ (Folder 83)
    - Cotton, Covetts, Covey, Cowden (Folder 84)
    - Cox (Folder 85)
    - Cozort (Cazort), Craft, Craig, Craighead, Crandell, Crawford, Crawley (Folder 86)
    - Creager (Cregar, Cregger) (Folder 87)
    - Cremeens, Crews, Crockett, Crotty, Crouch (Folder 88)
    - Croy (Folder 89)
    - Cruise, Cumiford, Cummings, Cunningham, Curry, Cuthrall (Folder 90)
    - Dabney (Folder 91)
    - Dailey, Dale, Dalton (Daulton), Dame, Damson (Damron, Daneron) (Folder 92)
    - Damewood (Folder 93)
    - Dancey (Dansey) (Folder 94)
    - Dangerfield, Daniel(s), Danieley, Dare (Folder 95)
    - Darnal(l) (Darnell, Darnel) (Folder 96)
    - Davidson (Folder 97)
    - Davis (Folder 98)
    - Dawson, Day, Dean, Deeds, Deel, Dehart (Folder 99)
    - Dempsey, Dennis, Dent, Denton, Devor, DeWeese, Deyerle (Folder 100)
    - Dial(s) (Diles), Dickens, Dickerson, Dickinson, Dill (Folder 101)
    - Dillon (Dillion) (Folder 102)
    - Dingess (Folder 103)
    - Dixon, Doak, Dobbins, Dole, Donnegan, Donavan, Dooley (Folder 104)
    - Dorsey, Doss, Dougherty, Douglas, Douthat, Dove, Dowdy, Doyle (Folder 105)
    - Draper, Drawdy, Drumheller, Duckett, Duffey, Duke (Folder 106)
    - Dulaney, Dunagan, Duncan, Dunford, Dunlap (Folder 107)
    - Dunn (Folder 108)
    - Durell, Durggins, Durham, Eagleston, Early (Folder 109)
  - Family Group Sheets (Box 3 of 12)
    - Easley (Folder 1)
    - Eastburn, Easter (Folder 2)
    - Eaton (Folder 3)
    - Ebach, Echols, Edgar, Edmonds, Edwards, Eisel, Elam (Folder 4)
    - Eldridge, Elkins, Ellett, Elliott, Ellis (Folder 5)
    - Ellison (Folder 6)
    - Ely, Emmons, England, English, Epling, Ernest, Erps (Folder 7)
    - Eschelberger, Estep, Evans, Faass, Fain, Fallis, Fanning, Fanwell (Folder 8)
    - Farley – Given names ‘A’ to ‘C’ (Folder 9)
    - Farley – Given names ‘D’ to ‘F’ (Folder 10)
    - Farley – Given names ‘G’ to ‘I’ (Folder 11)
    - Farley – Given names ‘J’ to ‘K’ (Folder 12)
    - Farley – Given names ‘L’ to ‘S’ (Folder 13)
    - Farley – Given names ‘T’ to ‘W’ (Folder 14)
    - Farmer, Farrington, Farris, Fary, Faulkner, Ferguson (Folder 15)
    - Ferrell, Fielder, Figgins, Fillinger (Folder 16)
    - Fink, Fisher, Fisk, Fizen, Fleming, Fleshman (Folder 17)
    - Fletcher (Folder 18)
    - lick, Flummer, Folding, Foley, Forbis, Forbush (Folder 19)
    - Ford, Foster, Fowler, Fox, Fraley, Francis (Folder 20)
    - Franklin, Frazier (Frashier), Freeman (Folder 21)
    - French (Folder 22)
    - French – Given names ‘A’ to ‘G’ (Folder 23)
    - French – Given names ‘H’ to ‘J’ (Folder 24)
    - Fry, Fuller, Gadd, Gardner, Garred, Garrett, Garretson (Folder 25)
    - Garten, Gask, Gastineau (Folder 26)
    - Gillie (Gilley, Gilly) (Folder 27)
    - Gatsley, Gautier, Gavet, George, Gibson, Giles, Gillan, Gillespie, Gilliam (Folder 28)
    - Gilpen, Givens, Glenn, Glover, Godfrey, Gogges, Goldsmith, Golladay, Gooch (Folder 29)
    - Goodall, Goode, Goodman, Goodwin, Gordan (Gordon) (Folder 30)
    - Gore (Folder 31)
    - Gose (Folder 32)
    - Goss, Gowens, Graffin, Graham, Grant, Gray, Graybeal, Grayson, Green(e) (Folder 33)
    - Greenup, Greer, Greever, Gregory, Griffith, Grim, Grisso, Grose, Gruan, Gussler, Guthridge (Folder 34)
    - Guthrey (Guthrie, Guthry) (Folder 35)
    - Gwinn, Hackett (Haskett), Hagan, Hager, Halcomb (Folder 36)
    - Hale(s) (Folder 37)
    - Hall, Halt, Ham(b)lin, Hambrick, Hamilton, Hammock (Folder 38)
    - Hammon(s), Hance, Hancock, Hand, Hanks, Hardbarger (Folder 39)
    - Hardman, Hare, Harless, Harmon (Harman), Harrell, Harris (Folder 40)
    - Harrison, Harry, Hart, Hartbarger, Hartnagle, Hartzog (Folder 41)
    - Harvey, Hatcher, Hatfield, Hatton, Hawkins, Hawley, Haynes (Folder 42)
    - Hays, Hayter, Hazelwood, Hearn, Heatherly, Hedrick, Helvy (Folder 43)
    - Henderson, Hendrick(s), Henry, Hensley, Hereford, Herbert, Hershey (Folder 44)
    - He(a)therington, Hickman, Hicks (Hix), Higginbotham, Hill, Hillman (Folder 45)
    - Hilton, Hines, Hoback, Hobbs, Hodge(s) (Hoge), Hogan, Holbrook (Folder 46)
    - Holdren (Holdron), Holland, Holliday, Holmes, Holroyd, Holston (Holstein) (Folder 47)
    - Holt, Holtzclaw, Homes, Honaker (Honicker, Honacre), Hood (Folder 48)
    - Hoon, Hooser, Hophmire, Hopkins, Hord (Hurd) (Folder 49)
    - Horsley (Folder 50)
    - Horton, Hose (Hoss), Houchins, Houff, Howard, Howe (Folder 51)
    - Hubbard, Hudgins, Hudson, Huff, Huffman (Folder 52)
    - Hugh(e)s (Folder 53)
    - Humphreys (Humphries), Hungate, Hunt, Hunter, Hurd, Hurst (Folder 54)
    - Hutchins, Hutchinson, Hutsell, Hutton, Hylton, Igo (Folder 55)
    - Ingram, Innis, Irick, Irvin, Isbell (Folder 56)
    - Jackson, Jacquith, James, Janell (Folder 57)
    - Jarvis, Jeffries, Jenks, Jennings, Jennet(t), Jewell, Jocken (Folder 58)
    - Johns(t)on – folder 1 of 2 (Folder 59)
  - Family Group Sheets (Box 4 of 12)
    - Johns(t)on – folder 2 of 2 (Folder 1)
    - Jones, Jordan, Journee, Journell (Jennelle), Justice (Justus, Justis), Kade (Folder 2)
    - Karnes, Keadle, Keatley, Keaton, Keen, Keenan (Folder 3)
    - Keffer, Kehoon, Kell(e)y, Kennedy, Kentley, Kessinger (Folder 4)
    - Kessler, Ke(i)ster, Ketherman, Ketron, Keyes, Kidd (Folder 5)
    - Kiely, Kimbo, Kincaid, Kinder, King, Kirk (Folder 6)
    - Kjelden, Klaber, Knode, Knutsen, Koch (Cock, Cook) (Folder 7)
    - Kristufek, Kyle, Lacy, Lafon, Lambert, Landcraft (Folder 8)
    - Landreth, Lane, Lanner, Laphew, Larew, Large (Folder 9)
    - Lawery, Lawson, Laxton, Layne, Layton, Leakv (Folder 10)
    - LeCompte, Ledford, Lee, Leffer, Leftwich (Folder 11)
    - Legans, Lemar, Lem(m)on, Leonard, Lesley (Leslie), Lester (Folder 12)
    - Leort(t), Lewey, Lewis, Lewty, Ligon, Lincus (Folder 13)
    - Lilly (Folder 14)
    - Lindsey, Link, Lipps, Little, Lively, Lloyd, Lockett, Lockridge (Folder 15)
    - Long (Folder 16)
    - Lowe, Lowrey, Lowther, Lucas, Luckadoo (Folder 17)
    - Luckin, Lumpkin, Lunsford, Lusk, Lybrook, Lynn (Folder 18)
    - Lyon, Lylton, McAdoo, McBride, McCall, McCarty (Folder 19)
    - McClaugherty, McClintock, McClung, McClure (Folder 20)
    - McComas (Folder 21)
    - McCom(m)ack (McComock), McCorkle, McCoy, McCraney (Folder 22)
    - McCraw (Folder 23)
    - McCurry, McDaniel, McDonald, McDowell, McElrath, McFarland (Folder 24)
    - McGavock, McG(h)ee, McGilda, McGinley, McGinnis (McGinnes), McGrady (Folder 25)
    - McGraw, McGruder, McGuire, McIntire, McKeand (McKeon), McKendree (Folder 26)
    - McKinn(e)y (McKenny), McKinsey (McKenzie, McKensey), McMahon, McManus, McMillan (McMillion), McNeer, McSwain (Folder 27)
    - Mabry, Madden, Maddy, Mangus, Mattafey, Mahan, Mahoney, Malcolm, Mallory, Mankin(s), Mann, Manser (Folder 28)
    - Manning, Manuel, Marchant, Marcum, Mardy, Marks, Marshall (Folder 29)
    - Martin (Folder 30)
    - Mason, Massie (Massey), Mattheny (Mathena), Matthews, Mattox, Maupin, Maxey, Maxwell, May, Maynard, Maynor, Mayo (Folder 31)
    - Mays, Meador, Meadows (Folder 32)
    - Mears, Meek, Mees (Miese, Miece, Meese, Meece), Mennix, Meredith (Folder 33)
    - Merrill, Merritt, Michael, Midley, Milam, Miller (Folder 34)
    - Mills, Millsap, Minnick, Minor, Minter, Mitchell, Mi(t)chum, Molds, Mollett, Mollica, Montgall, Montgomery (Folder 35)
    - Moore, Moran, Morgan, Morhead, Morris, Morrison, Moschlor, Moses, Motley, Moty, Moxley (Folder 36)
    - Moye, Muckelroy, Mullins, Munnell, Munsey (Muncey), Murdock, Murphy (Murfy) (Folder 37)
    - Music, Mustard, Myers, Nash, Neal (Neel), Nealy (Neely), Neiswander (Nicewander, Nicewonder) (Folder 38)
    - Nelson, Nepa, Nettle, Newberry (Newbury), Newkirk, Nibblett (Folder 39)
    - Newman, Nichols (Nickles), Nida, Noel, None (Nunn), Noonkister, Norris, Nowlin, O’Brien (Folder 40)
    - O’Dell, O’Donnell, O’Neal, O’Rayburn, Oberlin (Folder 41)
    - Oliphant, Oney, Orndorff, Orr, Osburn, (Osbourne, Osborne), Ould, Owen, Pack (Park) (Folder 42)
    - Packard (Folder 43)
    - Page (Folder 44)
    - Painter, Palmer, Pardue, Parker, Parsell, Pasley, Patrick, Patterson (Folder 45)
    - Payne (Pain(e)) (Folder 46)
    - Pearis (Folder 47)
    - Pearson, Peary (Peery, Perry), Peck, Pedigo, Pemberton, Pence (Folder 48)
    - Pendleton, Pennington, Pennix, Pensol, Penturff, Perdue, Perone (Folder 49)
    - Perrett (Perrat(t)), Peters, Petr(e)y (Petrie) (Folder 50)
    - Petty, Pewether, Phillips (Phipps, Fipps) (Folder 51)
    - Phillippi (Phillippy, Phillippie) (Folder 52)
    - Phlegar, Pickerall, Pierce (Pearce), Pigg, Pine(s), Piper, Plumb, Plumley, Poe, Poff, Pollard (Folder 53)
    - Pollett, Porter, Porterfield, Powell, Powers, Price, Profit, Pruett. Puckett, Purall, Purefoy (Folder 54)
    - Quinn, Quisenberry (Quesenberry), Raines (Rains, Raynes), Rainey, Ramey, Ramsey, Rat(c)liff (Folder 55)
    - Ravens, Rawlinson, Reaburn, Reece, Reed (Reid, Read, Reede), Rennle, Repass (Folder 56)
    - Retherford (Rutherford), Reynolds, Rhay (Ray, Rhey) (Folder 57)
    - Rhudy (Rudy) (Folder 58)
    - Rice, Rich, Richards, Richardson, Richmond (Richman), Rider, Riordan, Ritchie, Ritter, Roach, Roberts (Folder 59)
  - Family Group Sheets (Box 5 of 12)
    - Robinson, Rock, Rodefer, Rodes, Rogers, Roles (Folder 1)
    - Robertson (Folder 2)
    - Robinett (Folder 3)
    - Romine (Roman, Remine, Romeyne) (Folder 4)
    - Romine (Roman, Remine, Romeyne) – Given names ‘A’ to ‘F’ (Folder 5)
    - Romine (Roman, Remine, Romeyne) – Given names ‘G’ to ‘J’ (Folder 6)
    - Romine (Roman, Remine, Romeyne) – Given names ‘Jo to ‘N’ (Folder 7)
    - Romine (Roman, Remine, Romeyne) – Given names ‘O’ to ‘Z’ (Folder 8)
    - Rorrer, Rose, Rosene, Rosenow, Ross, Rowland (Roland), Rudd (Folder 9)
    - Rudisill, Ruggles, Rule, Runnion, Rupe (Roup), Rutledge (Folder 10)
    - St. Clair, St. Peter, Saavedra, Sad(d)ler, Sammons, Sampson (Folder 11)
    - Sands, Sanson, Santmeyer, Sanzini, Sarrett(e) (Starrett), Sartin (Folder 12)
    - Sarver, Sa(u)nders, Savage, Sayers, Scarborough, Schaen (Folder 13)
    - Schultz, Scott, Seal, See, Sellard, Seller (Folder 14)
    - Sence, Senter, Sesco, Sester, Setser, Shaffer (Folder 15)
    - Shanklin, Shannon, Sherwood, Sheets, Sheffey, Shell (Folder 16)
    - Shelton, Shepler, Sheppard, Shields, Shirley, Short (Folder 17)
    - Showalter, Shrader, Shrewsbury, Shufflebarger (Folder 18)
    - Shumate (Folder 19)
    - Sims (Simms, Symms) (Folder 20)
    - Shutt, Sier, Sikes, Silvers, Simpson (Folder 21)
    - Sincock, Sisson (Scisson, Scison), Sively, Sizemore, Skaggs, Skeens, Skeggs (Folder 22)
    - Slattery, Slemp (Schlemb), Sloan (Folder 23)
    - Smith (Folder 24)
    - Smoot, Snapp, Snavely, Snead (Sneed), Snidow, Snow (Folder 25)
    - Snodgrass, Snuffer, Snyder (Snider), Solesbury (Solisbury), Souder (Sowder), Southern (Folder 26)
    - Sowers, Spade, Spalding, Spangler (Folder 27)
    - Sparrow, Spencer, Spradling (Folder 28)
    - Stafford – folder 1 of 2 (Folder 29)
    - Stafford – folder 2 of 2 (Folder 30)
    - Stanley (Standly) (Folder 31)
    - Steel(e) (Folder 32)
    - Staton, Stegar, Stemple, Stephens (Folder 33)
    - Stewart (Stuart) – 1 of 2 (Folder 34)
    - Stewart (Stuart) – 2 of 2 (Folder 35)
    - Stepp, Stiley, Stiltner, Stinson, Stirman, Stoats, Stodgill, Stone, Stovall, Stover, Stowers, Strader (Folder 36)
    - Straley – Given names ‘A’ to ‘J’ (Folder 37)
    - Straley – Given names ‘L’ to ‘W’ (Folder 38)
    - Straley – Other Straleys (Folder 39)
    - Strode, Strong, Strother, Stump, Sturgeon, Styper, Suitor (Suter, Sutin) (Folder 40)
    - Summers (Sommers), Surface, Sutherland, Sutphin (Folder 41)
    - Sweeney, Sweptson, Swope, Sword, Tabb, Tabor (Folder 42)
    - Talbot, Taliaferro (Talferio, Talliaferri), Tanner, Tate, Taylor (Folder 43)
    - Terry (Folder 44)
    - Thomas (Folder 45)
    - Thompson – Given names beginning with ‘A’ (Folder 46)
    - Thompson – Given names ‘B’ to ‘D’ (Folder 47)
    - Thompson – Given names ‘E’ to ‘H’ (Folder 48)
    - Thompson – Given names ‘I’ to ‘J’ (Folder 49)
    - Thompson – Given names ‘L’ to ‘P’ (Folder 50)
  - Family Group Sheets (Box 6 of 12)
    - Thompson – Given names ‘R’ to ‘Z’ (Folder 1)
    - Thorn(e), Thornton, Thurmer, Tice, Tickle, Tiffany, Tilghman, Tiller, Tinker (Folder 2)
    - Tinsley, Todd, Toler, Tolley, Tol(l)iver, Tomlin, Tony, Totten, Tracy (Folder 3)
    - Trail, Trainle, Trimple, Triplett, Trollinger, Troutt, Trump, Tucker, Tuggle(s) (Folder 4)